Guide to the UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s UE.4.1.9
ULS Archives & Special Collections
UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals
1936-1990s
ULS Archives & Special Collections
United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America
UE.4.1.9
12 Linear Feet (approx. 10 boxes)
This series contains files on United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) District 9 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts.
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Previous Citation
UE National Office Records Relating to District 9 and District 9 Locals, 1936-1990s, UE.4.1.9, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Scope and Content Notes
District 9 of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America (UE) consisted of locals in Indiana and Michigan and are now part of the UE's Western Region. This series contains files on UE District 9 and its locals collected by the UE national office. Included are correspondence, publications, minutes, and news clippings regarding local strikes, events, and organizing efforts. Most of the correspondence is between UE national officers and district or local officers. This finding aid will be updated with a container listing as the project progresses.
Arrangement
This series has been arranged into two subseries. The first contains records pertaining to District 9. The other subseries contains records pertaining to specific locals within the district, and are further arranged numerically by local number into sections.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America in 1975, 1986, 1997, and 2001.
Related Material
UE District 9 Records, 1950s, UE.15.9, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
UE Local 925 Records, 1970s-1980s, UE.16.925, Archives & Special Collections, University of Pittsburgh Library System
Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Michigan -- History; Labor unions -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Michigan -- History -- 20th century; Labor unions -- Indiana -- History -- 20th century; Labor; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- United States -- History; Electric industry workers -- Labor unions -- Indiana -- History; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. District 9; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; Matles, James J.; Emspak, Julius
- District 9, 1.
  - District 9 Constitutions, 1938-1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - District 9 Constitutions, March 26, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - District 9 Constitutions, November 12, 1942-January 12, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - District 9 Constitutions, September 1, 1944-November 20, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - District 9 Constitutions, January 30, 1943-January 28, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - District 9 Constitutions, June 12, 1944-December 29, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - District 9 Constitutions, May 1942-October 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - District 9 Officers Lists, December 1941-October 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - District 9 Executive Council Minutes, December 10, 1938-January 2, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - District 9 Executive Council Minutes, June 24, 1944-May 21, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - District 9 Executive Council Minutes, January 27, 1950-January 10, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - District 9 Resolutions, January 2-June 24, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Resolution Regarding Wages and War Labor Board, January 2, 1944; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Eureka Vacuum Cleaner and Mechanics Educational Society of America Inter-union Rivalry, June 24, 1944; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Wages, June 24, 1944; 3.
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, June 25, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 24-December 11, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, April 15, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 28, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 27, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 26, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 27, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 25, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 25, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, October 7, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 27, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 27, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 29, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 21, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 29, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, October 10, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 19, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, September 24, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 26, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, October 8, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 18, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, October 21, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, October 6, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 27, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, October 23, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 26, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, October 22, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 25, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, March 25, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - District 9 District Membership Minutes, April 17, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - District 9 Resolutions, September 24, 1938-April 7, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 43)
    - Resolution Regarding Local 917 and Organization with Bertha Scott Letter to Jame Matles, October 10, 1938; 1.
    - Resolution Regarding Servel Strikes, March 29, 1939; 2.
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Education, March 28, 1939; 3.
    - Resolution Regarding Michgan, March 28, 1939; 4.
    - Resolution Regarding Staff Members and Indiana Congress of Industrial Organization, September 26, 1939; 5.
    - Resolution Regarding President Franklin D. Roosevelt, Political Action, No-Strike Pledge, Harry S. Truman, Missouri Valley Authority, Organization, Wages and Veterans, 6.
    - Resolution Regarding Foreign Policy and Henry Wallace, September 1946; 7.
    - Resolution Regarding Negotiations, September 1946; 8.
    - Resolution Regarding Staff Finances, September 1946; 9.
    - Resolution Regarding Factionalism, September 1946; 10.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, September 1946; 11.
    - Resolution Regarding Factionalism, March 28, 1947; 12.
    - Resolution Regarding Civil Liberties, March 26, 1947; 13.
    - Resolution Regarding Local 203 and Factionalism, 14.
    - Resolution Regarding Discrimination, 1948; 15.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action and Congress of Industrial Organization, 1948; 16.
    - Resolution Regarding Political Action, 17.
    - Resolution Regarding Labor Unity, April 7, 1956; 18.
    - Resolution Regarding Discrimination, 19.
    - Resolution Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization and Philip Murray, 20.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, December 14, 942-April 18, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 44)
    - Janet Barish Regarding Staff Finances, December 23, 1943; 1.
    - Barish Regarding Finances, September 14, 1945-May 28, 1946; 2-3.
    - Barish Telegram Regarding United Steelworkers of America, June 17, 1948; 4.
    - Barish Regarding Staff Finances, March 8, 1950; 5.
    - Merle Bennet Telegram Regarding General Executive Board, April 22, 1949; 6.
    - Neil Brant Regardign War Labor Board, December 14, 1942; 7.
    - Bill Cahn Regarding Labor History, July 1, 1947; 8.
    - Cahn Regarding Local Newspaper, October 11, 1948; 9.
    - Cahn Regarding Publicity, July 5, 1949; 10.
    - Cahn Regarding Inflation, April 18, 1951; 11.
    - James Carey Regarding Factionalism and General Electric Strikes, October 8, 1946; 12.
    - Carey Regarding Factionalism and Textile Workers, June 3, 1949; 13.
    - Larry Cover Regarding Local 905 and Pensions, June 4, 1950; 14.
    - Joseph Dermody Regarding Detroit Visit, June 16, 1944; 15.
    - Eve Dingel Regarding Fort Wayne, January 23, 943; 16.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, August 19, 1943-December 14, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 45)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Local 155 and Eby Department, August 19, 1943; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and General Electric Conference, December 21, 1943; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Grand Rapids, March 11, 1944; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Essex Wire and Dues, May 15, 1944; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Emspak Visit, July 3, 1944; 5.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Emspak Visit, July 6, 1944; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, July 11, 1944; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding General Motors Terre Haute, August 8, 1944; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Lear Avia and Staff Finances, August 11, 1944; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding District and Convention, September 7, 1944; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding St. Joseph Visit, September 5, 1944; 11.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Local 914, October 20, 1944; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances and Political Action Committee, October 25, 1944; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Automatic Instrument Organization, December 15, 1944; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, January 9, 1945; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Members, February 23, 1945; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Conscription, March 22, 1945; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, April 25, 1945; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Dues and Veterans, May 31-June 12, 1945; 19-20.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, June 20, 1945; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding District 9 Convention, September 18, 1945; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 825, General Executive Board and Factionalism, December 14, 1945; 23.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, March 5, 1946-December 22, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding Local 814 Strike Fund, March 5, 1946; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding National Federation for Constitutional Liberties, April 8, 1946; 2.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 933, May 13, 1946; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 911 and 914 Amalgamations, June 25, 1946; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, November 11, 1946; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 919 and Suspension, December 4, 1946; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 91 and 918, January 7, 1947; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, January 28, 1947; 8.
    - Emspak Secretary Regarding Tokheim and Finances, February 19, 1947; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, March 12, 1947; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding Staff Finances, May 5, 1947; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Radio Broadcasts, May 22, 1947; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 902 and Organization, August 1, 1947; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Steward's Conference, December 15, 1947; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding American Jewish Labor Council, February 16, 1948; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 926 and 935, and Per Capita, December 2, 1948; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Factionalism and Local 902, March 28, 1949; 17.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Local 931 with David Scribner Memo to Emspak, April 21, 1949; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Hoover and Belmont Strikes, June 7, 1949; 19.
    - Emspak Secretary Regarding Local 937, Research and Factionalism with June 6, 1949, Charles Kelly Letter to Emspak, June 8, 1949; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 1102 and Factionalism, September 27, 1949; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and United Farm Equipment Workers Locals, December 7, 1949; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding United Farm Equipment Workers Locals and Per Capita, December 19, 1949; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, December 22, 1949; 24.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, June 5, 1950-August 17, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Julius Emspak Regarding General Executive Board, June 5, 1950; 1.
    - Emspak Regarding Fair Employment Practices Commission with June 16, 1950, Report of FEPC-UE, June 20, 1950; 2.
    - Emspak Telegram Regarding Emspak Visit, October 18, 1950; 3.
    - Emspak Regarding 1950 UE Convention, October 23, 1950; 4.
    - Emspak Regarding Supplies, January 15, 1951; 5.
    - Emspak Regarding Political Action, March 12, 1951; 6.
    - Emspak Regarding High Treason, April 23, 1951; 7.
    - Emspak Regarding Political Action, May 16, 1951; 8.
    - Emspak Regarding Bonding and Locals 902 and 911, May 28, 1951; 9.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, February 5, 1952; 10.
    - Emspak Regarding UE Fighting Fund, July 30, 1952; 11.
    - Emspak Regarding Strike Fund, September 24, 1952; 12.
    - Emspak Regarding Blacklisting, February 13, 1953; 13.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and American Rubber Products with July 1, 1953, David Scribner Memo to Emspak, July 28, 1953; 14.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, September 2, 1953; 15.
    - Emspak Regarding Per Capita and District 9 Locals, November 18, 1953; 16.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 916 and Lawsuit, November 18, 1953; 17.
    - Emspak Secretary Regarding District 9 Meetings, January 28, 1954; 18.
    - Emspak Regarding Per Capita, Finances and District 9 Locals, February 24, 1954; 19.
    - Emspak Regarding Emspak Visit, October 19, 1954; 20.
    - Emspak Regarding Mill Town, December 13, 1954; 21.
    - Emspak Regarding Locals 911 and 914, February 11, 1955; 22.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 924 and Executive Board Meeting, April 14, 1955; 23.
    - Emspak Regarding General Executive Board and Local 911, September 9, 1955; 24.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, November 14, 1955; 25.
    - Emspak Regarding Local 905 and Per Capita, December 28, 1955; 26.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances and Gojack Trial, February 28, 1956; 27.
    - Emspak Regarding Labor Unity with Emspak Letter to All District 9 Locals, March 15, 1956; 28.
    - Emspak Regarding Finances, June 12, 1956; 29.
    - Emspak Regarding Emspak Visit, July 11, 1956; 30.
    - Emspak Regarding Buffalo Meeting, July 30, 1956; 31.
    - Emspak Regarding 1956 UE Convention, August 17, 1956; 32.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, June 23, 1944-March 10, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Albert Fitzgerald Regarding Decatur General Electric and Grievances, March 10, 1944; 1.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Richmond Decca, April 26,1944; 2.
    - Fitzgerald Secretary Regarding Richmond Decca, May 5, 1944; 3.
    - Fitzgerald Telegram Regarding Fort Wayne Phelps Dodge Strikes, November 28, 1944; 4.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District 9 Convention, March 25, 1946; 5.
    - Fitzberald Telegram Regarding Fitzgerald Visit, September 20, 1948; 6.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Local 118A Hayes Truck Appliance Negotiations, August 16, 1950; 7.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District 9 Convention, September 27, 1951; 8.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Fitzgerald Visit, January 4, 1952; 9.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Local 903 and Factionalism with June 26, 1952, Hoyte Thomas Letter to Fitzgerald, July 1, 1952; 10.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding District 9 Convention, October 8, 1952; 11.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Lynn General Electric, November 23, 1953; 12.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding New York Meeting, March 25, 1954; 13.
    - Fitzgerald Regarding Inter-union Rivalry, August 24, 1956; 14.
    - Henry Fiering Regarding Factionalism and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 23, 1956; 15.
    - W. B. Freeman Regarding Conscription, February 23, 1945; 16.
    - Dale Gaid Regarding Local 902 and Factionalism, July 1, 1946; 17.
    - Charlotte Hall Regarding Local 918 and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 13, 1951; 18.
    - Loren Houser Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization Conference, April 6, 1948; 19.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, March 8, 1944-October 29, 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Leo Jandreau Telegram Regarding Decatur General Electric and Grievances, March 8, 1944; 1.
    - William Johnson Regarding United Auto Workers Inter-union Rivalry, May 18, 1948; 2.
    - John Jones Regarding Joplin Vickeis, October 29, 1952; 3.
    - Selma Kaslick Regarding Brass Council, February 11, 1946; 4.
    - Kaslick Regarding Matles Visit, June 29, 1946; 5.
    - Charles Kelly Regarding Exide Negotiations and Factionalism, April 7, 1945; 6.
    - Ray Klausner Telegram Regarding District 9 Convention, March 13, 1950; 7.
    - Emma Koepnick Regarding Sear's Firing, July 7, 1948; 8.
    - Jim Lerner Telegram Regarding Horton and UE News, 9.
    - Helen Lief Regarding Furniture City Plating Negotiations, August 16, 1946; 10.
    - Frederick Livingston Regarding Essex Wire and Insurance, July 21, 1944; 11.
    - Molly Lynch Regarding Wages and Congress of Industrial Organizations, May 24, 1949; 12.
    - Frank Mavutz Regarding Local 931, Finances and Organization, May 1944; 13.
    - David Mates Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry with November 7, 1949, Arthur Hutchins Letter to James Carey and Local 937 Officer's Statement, November 11, 1949; 14.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, February 11, 1943-July 1, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - James Matles Regarding Staff Members and United Office and Professional Workers of America, February 11, 1943; 1.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Phelps Dodge Strikes, August 6, 1943; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 15, 1945; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Tokheim Pump, November 27, 1945; 4.
    - Matles Regarding General Executive Board, January 3, 1946; 5.
    - Matles Regarding Wire Industry, April 30, 1946; 6.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 3, 1946; 7.
    - Matles Regarding Training School, July 8, 1946; 8.
    - Matles Regarding Organization, July 22, 1946; 9.
    - Matles Regarding White Collar Workers, July 24, 1946; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, July 24, 1946; 11.
    - Matles Regarding Faunsworth, July 26, 1946; 12.
    - Matles Regarding Peru Organization, October 14, 1946; 13.
    - Matles Regarding Veterans and Phelps Dodge, November 21, 1946; 14.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Faunsworth, November 26, 1946; 15.
    - Matles Regarding District Convention, November 29, 1946; 16.
    - Matles Regarding District 9 Convention, December 5, 1946; 17.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding South Bend Singer Negotiations, May 5, 1947; 18.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, November 7, 1947-January 22, 1948; 19-20.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Staff Members, August 2, 1948; 21.
    - Matles Regarding Matles Visit, October 28, 1948; 22.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 12-July 1, 1949; 23-25.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, January 25, 1951-November 9, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - James Matles Regarding Staff Members, January 25, 1951; 1.
    - Matles Regarding UE Handbook, March 1, 1951; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, March 6, 1951; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, March 19, 1951; 4.
    - Matles Regarding Contracts, Philco and Wages, April 20, 1951; 5.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, July 24, 1951; 6.
    - Matles Telegram Regarding Local 931, August 1, 1951; 7.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Reports, September 27, 1951; 8.
    - Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, Wage Stabilization Board and Marion Machine Foundry, December 26, 1951; 9.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, February 18, 1952; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Finances and District 9 Bulltin, June 11, 1952; 11.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, Local 910 and Paducah Organization with June 19, 1952, William Ives Letter to Matles, June 24, 1952; 12.
    - Matles Regarding Essex Wire and Finances, July 14, 1952; 13.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members, IUE and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers inter-union Rivalry and Union City Westinghouse, July 17, 1952; 14.
    - Matles Regarding Humphrey Committee, July 29, 1952; 15.
    - Matles Regarding Finances and Locals 118 and 932 Strikes with October 21, 1951, Wilbur Penzian Letter to Julius Emspak and October 22, 1952, Penzian Letter to Ed Pratner, October 27, 1952; 16.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Meeting, November 3, 1952; 17.
    - Matles Regarding Finances and Local 118F Strikes, November 7, 1952; 18.
    - Matles Regarding Finances and Staff Members, December 2, 1952; 19.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Members and Power Equipment, December 3, 1952; 20.
    - Matles Regarding International Harvester Strikes, December 18, 1952-March 11, 1953; 21-22.
    - Matles Regarding Staff Finances, March 30, 1953; 23.
    - Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, May 25, 1953; 24.
    - Matles Regarding Wayne Pump and Inter-union Rivalry, June 4, 1953; 25.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, June 16, 1953; 26.
    - Matles Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry, November 9, 1953; 27.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, March 17, 1954-September 9, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - James Matles Secretary Regarding Local 118F and Finances, March 17, 1954; 1.
    - Matles Regarding Mueluer Trial, August 11, 1954; 2.
    - Matles Regarding Matles Visit, September 10, 1954; 3.
    - Matles Regarding Local 931 and Staff Members, September 24, 1954; 4.
    - Matles Regarding Locals 451, 910 and 931, February 11, 1955; 5.
    - Matles Regarding Magnavox, Capehart and Inter-union Rivalry, March 14, 1955; 6.
    - Matles Regarding Finances, April 27, 1955; 7.
    - Matles Regarding Clyde Wirlpool and International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry, May 6, 1955; 8.
    - Matles Regarding International Association of Machinists Inter-union Rivalry and Whirlpool, May 31, 1955; 9.
    - Matles Regarding Local 933 and Inter-union Rivalry, September 7, 1955; 10.
    - Matles Regarding Local 813 and Inter-union Rivalry, September 9, 1955; 11.
  - District 9 Incoming John Gojack Correspondence, October 19, 1944-March 22, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Edward Matthews Regarding Westinghouse and St. Joseph with Setember 10, 1944, Jack Voylaan Letter to Matthews, October 19, 1944; 1.
    - William Mayo Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization, January 11, 1946; 2.
    - Clifford McAvoy Regarding Political Action, February 3, 1947; 3.
    - McAvoy Regarding District 9 Convention, March 10, 1947; 4.
    - Elizabeth Moore Regarding International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Inter-union Rivalry, March 4, 1944; 5.
    - Charles Munford Regarding Local 918, Factionalism and IUE Inter-union Rivalry, June 13, 1951; 6.
    - Don Pinkston Regarding IUE Inter-union Rivalry and Factionalism, October 30, 1947; 7.
    - Basil Pollitt Regarding Cupehart Suit and Finances, March 22, 1954; 8.
    - David Ratner Regarding Supplies, August 30, 1945; 9.
    - Ratner Regarding Finances and Local 931, March 28, 1946; 10.
    - Ratner Regarding Finances, January 10-17, 1950; 11-12.
    - Ratner Regarding 1954 UE Convention, September 24, 1951; 13.
    - Ratner Regarding Finances and United Farm Equipment Workers, 14.
    - Ben Riskin Regarding Phelps Dodge Strikes and International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers Strikes, May 11, 1946; 15.
    - Riskin Regarding Publicity, October 7, 1948; 16.
    - August Scholle Regarding Congress of Industrial Organization and Policital Action Committee, September 26, 1945; 17.
    - Hardy Scott Regarding Local 75 Distributive Processing and Office Workers of America, February 15, 1951; 18.